<?xml version="1.2" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Apini Playable Race</name>
	<author>Jack7D1</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>sera.apinialienrace</packageId>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
			<displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<description>
Requires most recent version of Alien Race Framework.
Patched version supporting 1.0, 1.1 and 1.2!

This mod lets you play as a race of sentient giant bees called Apini.
Features:
• Bees as a plyable race.
• Apini and Azuri neolithic factions.
• Custom Bee name lists and backgrounds.
• Apini scenario to start with (neolithic)...
• ...Or play as a horde of apini (and human) eating azuri! (there's no reason i should be excited about this)
• Beeswax and honey production
• Bee clothing and a helmet.
• Beeswax Candles for atmosphere.
• Honeycomb Beds filled with rejuvenating honey.
• Already contains a CE patch.
• Is compatible with RimBees.

Credits:
Chjees – C#
Xen – A16 EPOE patch
Erdelf – HAF Framework
ZE – Azuri Sprites + B18 update
Sera/Miss bones – Apini race mod base and original creator
Lamp - some art assets
Rabbitt - some art assets
Apini Discord - Loving fans and helpful creators
Ykara – Inspiration (EPOE mod maker)
Rah – Inspiration (RBSE mod maker)
Bees - Making delicious honey
Saebbi - Making part of the Combat Extended patch.
Zaltys - Updating to RimWorld 1.0.
Almantuxas - Making less broken after 1.0 update, updating to 1.1, adding to and modifying the Combat Extended patch aswell as some other patches and current maintainer.
Trisscar - Texture for the Daisy plant.
Diana Winters - Patching mod to 1.2

Issues remaining:
• Because RimWorld is RimWorld, there's an issue with the RimBees patch, that the Apini wax doesn't actually get removed (even though the operation is supposed to do that).
• Mood bonus from bee aprons (was this ever implemented?)
• Scyther Blade surgery (hard to add, scythers do not drop blades in 1.0)
• Counter for the vats.
• Stardew, and related surgeries. Could not find sources for them.
• FactionDefs and PawnKindDefs may need work. I focused on getting this working, some values might be out of whack.
• Honey Planter Hydroponics-thing has a texture, but not yet implemented.
• Lady beeliens might still spawn with the drone trait (and had to remove a backstory to fix this issue). This exists because of an issue with Humanoid Alien Races.
• Should reintroduce Apitech Mutagen as a drug.
• Honey vats of any kind get an empty line in the inspect string. Throws an error, but isn't gamebreaking (I think).
	</description>
</ModMetaData>