<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Apini Playable Race</name>
	<author>Sera</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>sera.apinialienrace</packageId>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
			<displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<description>
v4.29h-d - an update to 1.1 for the UNOFFICIAL update of the UNOFFICIAL 1.0 update
Requires most recent version of Alien Race Framework.

This mod lets you play as a race of sentient giant bees called Apini.
Features:
• Bees as a plyable race.
• Apini and Azuri neolithic factions.
• Custom Bee name lists and backgrounds.
• Apini scenario to start with (neolithic)...
• ...Or play as a horde of apini (and human) eating azuri! (there's no reason i should be excited about this)
• Beeswax and honey production
• Bee clothing and a helmet.
• Beeswax Candles for atmosphere.
• Honeycomb Beds filled with rejuvenating honey.
• Already contains a CE patch.
• Is compatible with RimBees.

Credits:
Chjees – C#
Xen – A16 EPOE patch
Erdelf – HAF Framework
ZE – Azuri Sprites + B18 update
Sera – Apini race mod base and original creator
Lamp - some art assets
Rabbitt - some art assets
Apini Discord - Loving fans and helpful creators
Ykara – Inspiration (EPOE mod maker)
Rah – Inspiration (RBSE mod maker)
Bees - Making delicious honey
Saebbi - Making part of the Combat Extended patch.
Zaltys - Updating to RimWorld 1.0.
Almantuxas - Making less broken after 1.0 update, updating to 1.1, adding to and modifying the Combat Extended patch aswell as some other patches and current maintainer.
Trisscar - Texture for the Daisy plant.

_____v4.29g ... v4.29h-b 1.0 Beta notes_____
Changes:
• Fixed reconstruct surgeries. They weren't working up until this update.
• Added compatibility for Enhanced Prosthetics and Organ Engineering (tl;dr EPOE). Report any issues!
• Added compatibility for Rah's Bionics and (tl;dr RBSE). Report any issues!
• Fixed 2 issues with the RimBees patch. 
• If you're using Consolidated Traits, Apini yet again spawn with the green thumb trait and never spawn with the brown thumb trait, Azuri have a chance of spawning with the brown thumb trait.
• Fixed installing power claws for Apini and Azuri on the bodypart that's the human equivalent of a FOOT.
• Made surgeries more in line with vanilla. But installing a limb onto a beelien is still more difficult than on a human.
• Added Apitech Mutagen to the resources used in the reconstruction surgeries, at the same time rebalanced those surgeries.
• Fixed an issue with EdB Prepare Carefully which was causing Apini plants to appear in the Food tab.
• Added support for wearing apparel from the Vanilla Armour Expanded mod.
• Added support for wearing apparel from the Vanilla Apparel Expanded mod.
• Added support for wearing apparel from the Simple Slavery mod.
• Removed (commented them out) Apitech prosthesis and organs, because they don't have a use. Should readd them with surgeries n' stuff in the future. At the same time reduced the research cost of the Apitech research project to make up for the removal.
• (TL;DR Medical System Expansion is now compatible) Added surgeries for installing prosthesis from Medical System Expansion when it is detected. I am unsure if I didn't make any mistakes while patching, so please report any issues.
• Added more Combat Extended patches: one for natural armor coverage and leather rebalance.
• Reconstruction (now enhancement) surgeries now take their respective item instead of mutagen.
• Readded some apitech items.
• Added more mutations and surgeries.
• Changed item, hediff and surgery descriptions and labels.
• Fixed Consolidated Traits patch. Should work correctly now.
• Nerfed harvest yield and plant work speed of Apinis. Now you can't just have one Apini feeding 20 people.
• Modified Azuri stats.
• Changed research costs.
• Changed some honey effects. Made honey effects less potent but last longer.
• Removed (commented out) Apitech Mutagen, since it doesn't have a use anymore. Should make it a drug later on that'd give random enhancements.
• Updated the Combat Extended patch to be up-to-date with CE 1.6.
• Updated the beelien body. No longer will Apini and Azuri wear 100 scarfs from Vanilla Apparel Expanded or 100 scrap shoulderpads from Apparello.
• Increased combat power of all pawn kinds (normal, overseer, pirate and trader). Expect to see less of Apini and Azuri.
• Updated the Combat Extended's patch to have correct armor values.
_____ v4.29h-c ... v4.29h-d 1.1 Beta notes_____ (when am i going to make a 4.30 update? no clue)
• Updated the mod to Rimworld 1.1. Can still use the mod on 1.0, but the 1.0 version won't be getting changes.
• Fixed the honeycomb beds throwing a tantrum in the error log for not having a owner label.
• Fixed the fill-one-at-a-time bug for filling vats with nectar.

Issues remaining:
• Because RimWorld is RimWorld, there's an issue with the RimBees patch, that the Apini wax doesn't actually get removed (even though the operation is supposed to do that).
• Mood bonus from bee aprons (was this ever implemented?)
• Scyther Blade surgery (hard to add, scythers do not drop blades in 1.0)
• Counter for the vats.
• Stardew, and related surgeries. Could not find sources for them.
• FactionDefs and PawnKindDefs may need work. I focused on getting this working, some values might be out of whack.
• Honey Planter Hydroponics-thing has a texture, but not yet implemented.
• Lady beeliens might still spawn with the drone trait (and had to remove a backstory to fix this issue). This exists because of an issue with Humanoid Alien Races.
• Should reintroduce Apitech Mutagen as a drug.
• Honey vats of any kind get an empty line in the inspect string. Throws an error, but isn't gamebreaking (I think).
	</description>
</ModMetaData>