<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>Apini Continued</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>sera.apinialienrace</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://discord.gg/CJwh6YZk4G</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ApiniNews_1_3_0_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Hello and I hope you're enjoying the Apini mod! |Version 1.3 is upon us and that means that development for 1.2 has frozen. While it'll remain present for backcompatibility, all future changes will be in the latest version. This is the first time that I've given hugslib's update thingy a whirl so I hope this works well! As a result now I can better relay major changes so that there's less confusion. |For more updates and/or a direct line to development, visit our discord at the link above! There is a verification channel that you have to send a message in proving you aren't a spambot, but once you do that you get access. |Again thank you for being one of the thousands who share my love for bees :> |Jack7D1 "Ely"</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ApiniNews_1_3_0_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Hello! On August 21st, 2020 Apini Continued was first published to the steam workshop! It first started out as a simple revival of the mod with a few bugfixes, but I never would have expected it to become so much more than that! |To celebrate Apini Continued's birthday some new features have been added! Most notably: Insectoids now have a truce function. While previously they were infinitely forgiving, now if you anger the hive they stay mad! This is explained further in the learning helper. |Speaking of, the learning helper got a big upgrade! This should make honeymaking and beeswax more accessible to newer players. Thank you for all your support and making this year incredibly fun! |Jack7D1 "Ely"</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>